(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I was going to mention it
at the time,
(Sheldon:)but then I thought, some day,
(Sheldon:)this might be a teachable moment.
Ahh!
But I...?! You...?! How...?!
What?!
(Amy:)Sheldon, that was diabolical.
(Leonard:)I know.
(Sheldon:)And it wasn't easy.
(Sheldon:)Do you have any idea what it's like
to wait for years,
(Sheldon:)and never know if you're going
to finally get satisfaction?
(Lucy:)Wow.
(Raj:)You're even prettier than Penny said.
(Raj:)I can't believe a girl like you
doesn't have a boyfriend.
(Leonard:)Well, I don't.
(Raj:)I don't believe you.
You're lying to me!
(Leonard:)What?
(Raj:)It's okay. I have no morals,
and I'm desperately lonely.
(Raj:)I'll be the other man if you want
a little something-something
(Raj:)on the side.
What is wrong with you?!